Guide to the Admissions Reference Collection, 1949-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
Admissions Reference collection 1949-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
0.5 linear feet Extent: approx. 500 Items
The Admissions Reference Collection contains files of printed matter, statistics, and other material concerning admission. This collection was compiled from a variety of sources by the University Archives for use in reference and research.
UA.01.11.0079
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the University Archives to use this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Admissions Reference Collection was acquired by the University Archives over time.
Collection Overview
The Admissions Reference Collection contains files concerning admission and recruitment. Materials include class profiles and other statistics and compilations, memoranda, brochures, application forms, clippings, newsletters, reports, fact sheets and other publicly distributed material.
Contents of Collection
- Container List
  - Administration, circa 1960-1986 (Box 1)
  - Application forms [blanks], 1960s (Box 1)
  - Brochures, circa 1949/54-2000/01 (Box 1)
  - Brochures, Blue Devil Days, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Brochures, campus visits, undated (Box 1)
  - Brochures, financial aid, 1960-1970 (Box 1)
  - Brochures and handouts, miscellaneous, undated (Box 1)
  - Class profiles, 1954-2001 (Classes of 1959-2005, incomplete) (Box 1)
  - Clippings, circa 1972-2001 (Box 1)
  - Cumulative statistics and compilations, 1958-1989 (Box 1)
  - Report of the faculty committee on admissions, 1953 (Box 1)
  - Trinity College of Arts & Sciences - Fact sheets [on Departments] 1985 (Box 1)
  - Trinity College of Arts & Sciences - Profiles of Departments & Programs, 1986/87 (Box 1)
  - Trinity College of Arts & Sciences - Profiles of Departments & Programs, 1987/88 (Box 1)